[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Jacksons aunt, who made one of their wedding cakes in the film Steel Magnolias?", "correct_answer": "Fern", "incorrect_answers": ["Nina", "Ouiser", "Shelby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Devilfish, a large species of ray, also called manta, was named such due to which of these characteristic features?", "correct_answer": "Two pointed lobes on each side of the head", "incorrect_answers": ["Its pointed tail", "Its hunting habits", "Extended, winglike fins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did the word golf originate?", "correct_answer": "Scotland", "incorrect_answers": ["Ireland", "Canada", "Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the first US national antismoking coalition, formed in 1964?", "correct_answer": "National Interagency Council on Smoking and Health", "incorrect_answers": ["Action on Smoking and Health", "None of these", "National Clearinghouse for Smoking and Health"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The volcanoes - Akan, Aso, Mount Fuji and Rausu are located in this country.", "correct_answer": "Japan", "incorrect_answers": ["Malaysia", "North Korea", "Indonesia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All of these substances but one are a safe way to get rid of ants in the house. Which is the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Wine", "incorrect_answers": ["Cider vinegar", "Windex mixed with ivory soap", "Whole cloves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Antibiotics are used to treat virus infections in animals and humans but are ineffective in plant virus infections.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Arthralgia is a severe heart disorder.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is one of the benefits of chewing gum.", "correct_answer": "Helps resist the urge to smoke", "incorrect_answers": ["Helps taste", "Enhances the function of the lungs", "Alleviates stuffed nose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This British car manufacturer produces high performance vehicles. The company was founded in 1989.", "correct_answer": "McLaren", "incorrect_answers": ["Land Rover", "Rolls-Royce", "Jaguar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Canadian lake is the largest in the world, located on an island?", "correct_answer": "Nettilling Lake", "incorrect_answers": ["Aral", "Winnipeg", "Michigan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A modem is both an input and an output device.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]